I think with every new development
Paradigm really with every new
technology that comes along the first
thing we do is we try to use that
technology to improve the way we do
things today and probably like a recent
example of that is cloud right Cloud
came along that was a great opportunity
to lift and shift and get a bunch of
boosts out of it but rather in Cloud
native software development we
understand that if you were to really
change the way you build software and
embrace microservices and elasticity in
your sort of infrastructure then you can
really squeeze the most out of it and so
I think with AI if you look at what's
happening today I think we're doing the
same thing again and so there is what I
think of as AI assisted software
development and that is uh using these
like amazing tools like co-pilot and
test Generations but the real
opportunity for developing software in
the era of AI is to think about AI
native software development what is the
software development process that you
would want to have if you were to think
about it from first principles and
really build the whole methodology at